http://www.girlsaskguys.com/privacy-policy

Food & Beverage
How Do I Look?
INTRODUCTION
GirlsAskGuys' Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using GirlsAskGuys, located at www.girlsaskguys.com and its directly associated domains (collectively, "GirlsAskGuys" or "website"). By using or accessing GirlsAskGuys, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. GirlsAskGuys respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our website (website also includes “mobile application”) only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at GirlsAskGuys’ website. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@girlsaskguys.com.
PART I. INFORMATION COLLECTION
GirlsAskGuys collects information through our website at several points. We may collect the following information about primary visitors: email address, gender, date of birth, zip code and country.
We may collect the following general data that is not personally identifiable information user name and password. We collect demographic data in order to refine local search criteria when you interact with other members. We collect this information through registration forms. The information is collected voluntarily. To receive our products and services, an email address, a username, date of birth zip code and country are requested to avoid fraudulent activity, prevent abuse of site and its contents and maintain records for your use. Other information we request is optional.
We do employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user’s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable GirlsAskGuys to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. Our cookies do not have an expiration date. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. We also use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to GirlsAskGuys. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser.
When you enter GirlsAskGuys, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all GirlsAskGuys users. We also collect website use information as you interact with our website, including but not limited to asking and/or answering questions, sending or receiving instant messages, writing editorials, articles and comments. You post this User Content, as defined in the GirlsAskGuys Terms of Use, on the website at your own risk. Although we allow you to set your privacy options that limit access to your pages, questions and answers, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to disclose your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the website will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the website. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.
If you choose to use our “email a question” service to send a friend a question, we will ask you for your name and your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email, which includes the question. GirlsAskGuys stores this information to send this one-time email, to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at privacy@girlsaskguys.com to request that we remove this information from our database.
Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on GirlsAskGuys is a violation of the GirlsAskGuys Terms of Use and should be reported to privacy@girlsaskguys.com.
Children Under Age 13
Our Services are not directed to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 without obtaining parental consent. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13 on our Services, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we may have collected any such personal information on our Services, please notify us at privacy@girlsaskguys.com
PART II. INFORMATION USAGE
Some information collected by GirlsAskGuys will be displayed within your user profile so that other members can interact with you.
Users who provide information may occasionally receive email announcements and newsletters, if they opt in. Registered users will, upon request, receive additional announcements from us about products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Registered users may also receive emails from GirlsAskGuys to communicate new services, updates offered by GirlsAskGuys that we think our users may find valuable. Users may also receive notifications in email format, when a question that is asked or bookmarked is updated with an answer.
Our default privacy settings limit the information displayed in your profile to other users of the site. Users can choose to modify this limit as they deem necessary. Users can even share information, ask questions anonymously without displaying their personal information, including their user names. Users can also change, update, or delete any personal information anytime by going to their account settings. Such updates will take effect immediately. Users who wish to deactivate their accounts may do so by contacting us at privacy@girlsaskguys.com. Any deleted information including but not limited to User information, user content or user accounts may be kept in a backup copy for a reasonable amount of time, in some cases due to legal regulations. Such information will not generally be available on the website.
The username, thumbnail image and location may be displayed in various parts of the website including but not limited to search results, members lists and user account pages. Such member information is displayed so that other members can see who answered or asked a question or so that friends can find friends in our website. Also note that the extent of the personal information displayed is limited to what users choose to display.
We may use profile information based on age, gender and location to promote news updates or products to display relevant advertisements or announcements.
We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. Third parties may also use pixels to collect non-personally identifiable information from emails that the user opens. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at https://www.networkadvertising.org. To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit https://www.aboutads.info/choices.
We offer links to other websites. Please note: When you click on links to other websites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours. GirlsAskGuys is not responsible for the content, terms or policies of any site that we link to.
Our website offers chats, ability to write editorials, articles, to send messages, to post questions, answers and comments. Please be advised that information posted in these venues becomes public knowledge.
We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the GirlsAskGuys service or using the GirlsAskGuys name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.
If our policy on information collection or uses changes, we will advise you by updating this page and include a date of revision.
PART III. ACCESS TO INFORMATION
Users may access their own personal information and update, change, and delete any part of it to which they are allowed to make updates to. If users need to change, update or remove information to which they don't have access to, they may contact us about these inaccuracies through our Contact Us page. Users may delete their information from our database by canceling their membership within their account section.
PART IV. PROBLEM RESOLUTION
Your use of GirlsAskGuys, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. If problems arise, users may contact GirlsAskGuys by email. We are committed to resolving disputes within 72 hours.
PART V. DATA STORAGE AND SECURITY
We use reasonable security measures that are designed to protect personal information from accidental loss, disclosure, misuse, and destruction. Please be aware, however, that no data security measures can be guaranteed to be completely effective. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you provide to us. You transmit information to us at your own risk.
PART VI. LINKS
GirlsAskGuys may contain links to other websites. While we monitor these links carefully, We are not responsible for contents, terms of use, or the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by GirlsAskGuys.
PART VII. THIRD PARTY ADVERTISEMENT
Some advertisements on GirlsAskGuys are sometimes delivered directly to users by third party advertisers. These advertisers automatically receive your IP address and may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content by collecting information (not personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits. By doing this the advertising network recognizes your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on GirlsAskGuys. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by GirlsAskGuys and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers. To block third-party cookies, please refer to your internet browser's help section. For more information and a full list of third-party advertising companies please contact us.
PART VIII. MODIFICATIONS TO THIS POLICY
We may modify this Policy in our discretion at any time. If we modify this Policy, we will post the new policy or any changes on this site and update the “Last Updated” date above. Your use of GirlsAskGuys after the later of (i) the date modifications to this Policy are posted on this site and (ii) the date such modifications are set to take effect, constitutes acceptance of the Policy, as modified, and from that time your use of GirlsAskGuys will be subject to the Policy, as modified.
Cast Your Vote Why do you get “high”?
Do you care 9/11 happened yesterday?
How would you feel if a girl went out with another guy while you two were dating?
What are you currently reading, or was the last book you read?
Who’s prettiest to you? What feature about them attracts you?
Show All
Top MHO%Top Xpers
Last 30 days Top MHO% ?
Last 30 days Top Xpers ?
Join with {0} Loading...
